Amanda Seale Show. Today's Figgup Figgup goes to classic hip-hop dance moves. An Alabama woman
by the name of Shariah Taylor credits Lil' Kim's dance moves from Mobb Deep's 1999 Quiet Storm
remix for saving her life during a shooting. Let's take a listen. So I'm getting to the car.
I hear fire, fire, fire, fire. So I'm ducking, I'm dodging, I'm dodging, I'm dodging, I'm ducking.
Oh man. Doing Lil' Kim. Oh okay, all right. So I see. Okay, I'm doing it now. Okay,
I can see how that would work. I see how that could work. I see how that could work. Yeah.
Hot damn ho. Here we go again. So hip-hop dance moves are saving lives and we're going to give
a big up to that. Today's letdown goes to a clueless cosmetic company. Popular beauty content
created by the name of Gloria George called out Youthphoria accusing the makeup brand of creating
a foundation resembling black face paint. Here's what she had to say. When we say that we want you
guys to make shades for us, we don't mean to go to the lab and ask for a minstrel show black.
What we mean is to take the browns that you have made, create undertones and do what you need to do
in the lab so it's a darker shade of black. Who is looking at this stuff being like, yeah,
let's do that because it costs money to fail in these spaces. They're like, you're either Alicia Keys
or Alek Wek. Like there's just no, that's it. And then people got the nerve to say DEI is a problem.
This is a prime example.